# Furqan Babar



furganbabarpk@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/mrrajputpak



03006691987



https://mrrajputpak.github.io/portfolio/

# Summary

Hi, Its Furqan. I am a Professional Website Designer.

WordPress:

I have been working with WordPress for 4 years and have developed a wide range of sites, from small personal blogs to large corporate websites. I am comfortable working with all aspects of WordPress, from installing and setting up a new site to customizing themes and plugins. I am also experienced in working with WooCommerce, the popular eCommerce platform that runs on top of WordPress. JavaScript:

I have been working with JavaScript for more than 1 year and have created many sites using JS. I am a professional MERN Stack developer at SJ Empower PVT LTD. If you are looking for someone to develop a website for you using JS, then I would be happy to help. Feel free to get in touch with me.

# **Experience**



## **MERN Stack developer**

SJ Empowers (Pvt) Ltd Nov 2022 - Present (3 months)



SJ Empowers (Pvt) Ltd Nov 2022 - Present (3 months)

## **Education**



#### GC University Faisalabad

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science 2018 - 2022

## **Licenses & Certifications**

Certified with WeLoveNoCode | No-code Tool: Wordpress - WeLoveNoCode 1673936319850x798859583202263000?red=1

#### Skills

WordPress Design • Templates • HTML5 • Plugins • Front-End Development • JavaScript • React.js • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Bootstrap